Customer Service| Business Development |Sales| Marketing| Lead Generation

37, Community Road, Yaba Lagos Nigeria

Tel: +234 8139621732 Email: itopawosoji@gmail.com

AWOSOJI, Grace Enny

PROFILE

A self-driven, passionate, talented, result-oriented, business-minded professional with excellent managerial skills, gained through 7years+ experience in Customer Service, Business Development, Sales and Marketing across various sectors. I proficiently handle areas such as high-level client management, sales and marketing.

PROFESSIONAL FORTE

Customer Experience | Customer Loyalty | Data & Information Management | Client Surveys | pre-and post-paid Support |
Documentation | Due Diligence | IT Skills | B2B Sales | B2C Sales | Marketing | Market Trends
HNIs Management | Client Engagement | Problem resolution | Lead Conversion | Brand Management |
| Needs Assessment | Marketing Campaigns | Team Management | Premium Marketing |
| Perception & Impression Management | Vendor Management | Service Level Agreements | Telesales | Human Resources

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Longrich Biosciences Abuja.

Role: Sales Representative (Jul. 2016 – date)

Key Responsibilities:

- Develop and manage marketing strategies to drive brand awareness in the Nigerian market.
- In collaboration with Sales, provide marketing plan consultation to key dealers to ensure integrated marketing efforts are optimized to enhance sales volumes.
- Develop tactics such as advertising, local partnerships, branding through social media/digital marketing, etc.
- · Visiting key clients, pitching opportunities for managing execution of approved marketing plans
- Assist network partners in promoting Longrich brand at trade shows and events
- Design and construct necessary event properties and manage the use of those assets
- Coordinate bi-monthly regional update meetings with distributors and retailers
- Serve as liaison between the company and distributors
- Create digital content such as blog and social media posts (Facebook, Instagram) for client attraction
- Distributor/Dealer Tools Management
- Assist with dealer certification and incentive programs
- Provides input for training, education/competency, and technical assistance to the sales force and dealers

Gracious Retail Distribution Ltd., Port Harcourt

Role: Business Manager (Aug. 2014 – June 2016)

Key Responsibilities:

- Drive business objectives to achieve monthly sales and revenue targets
- Initiated sales of products by establishing contact and developing relationships with prospects
- Maintained relationships with clients by providing support, information, and guidance; researching and recommending new opportunities; recommending profit and service improvements.
- Attended meetings with potential customers and closed sales.

Key Achievement:

Raised customer base from 4 to 26 in 4 months

Water Sewage Department, Federal Airport Authority of Nigeria (FAAN)

Role: Laboratory Technologist (Jul- 2012 - Jul 2014)

Key Responsibilities:

- Used established lab protocol to perform laboratory tests and correctly log the results of those tests
- Determined sample validity within the first 20 minutes of receiving the sample
- Identified and diagonised and issues that may arise with the laboratory equipment

- Verified all test results and ensure that they are correctly matched with the specimen
- Labeled and organized all tests appropriately to make sure that they are easily retrievable
 Key Achievement:

Most Dutiful and Punctual Female IT Student.

Tito- B Pharmaceutical Ltd.

Role: Pharmacist Assistant (Aug 2007- Feb 2009)

Key Responsibilities:

- Dispensed prescription medication and other medical products to patients under direction of licensed pharmacist
- Counted pills, labels bottles, prices, and compounds medications to prepare prescriptions for patients as directed
- Performed administrative duties, including answering phones, receiving and inputting prescription orders, operating cash registers, and restocking inventory
- Supplied patients with information and education on their prescriptions
- Monitored prescription-filling process to ensure compliance with relevant regulations and pharmacy policies
- Liaised with healthcare providers and patients to obtain correct prescription information
- Took inventory of drugs on hand and recorded results
- Placed orders for additional drugs as directed by the pharmacist
- Maintained electronic patient information
- Prepared billing information for medications
- Completed patients' sales transactions for purchase of prescription and over-the-counter medications as well as other pharmaceutical products

EDUCATION

Ogun State Institute of Technology, Ogun State Environmental Biological Sciences	2019
Kwara State Polytechnic, Ilorin, Kwara State Science Laboratory Technology	2010

SKILLSET

- Practical Knowledge of persuasive and Influencing skills
- Effective negotiation and conflict resolution skills.
- Dogged and resolute goals getter
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills with an affinity for problem solving
- Proficiency in the use of Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint.
- Persuasive and excellent impression management skills
- Collaborative and flexibility skills
- People Management skills
- Sound sense of judgement and common sense

REFEREES

On Request